#### \_

### Muhammad Fariz Fahrezi

I was a graduate of SMK country 2 cilegon with an industrial chemistry major, I had expertise in lab equipment and an understanding of chemical processes. I have experience in doing data analysis and testing the quality of chemical products. I have also been able to adapt quickly to changes in the environment and demands of the industry



Serang, Banten, Indonesia



## Work Experience

September 2022 -Oktober 2022

#### Quality Control PT. INDONESIA POWER SURALAYA PGU

Sampling, preparation and analysis of coal quality using TGA, CHN Analyzer, Automatic Calorimeter, and Sulfur determinator. As well as testing the analysis of water used in production

## **Organizational Experience**

2022 - 2023

#### Organisasi Siswa Intra Sekolah

- · Working together on a single year program of student labor
- · Discussions during meetings for a work program
- Are responsible for running a work program
- · Organize and carry out activities to promote student creativity at school

#### Education

2020 - 2023

SMK Negeri 2 Cilegon Indutrial Chemistry

#### Hard Skills

- Laboratory Skills
- P&ID
- Ms. Excel
- Ms. Word
- Ms. Powerpoint
- Figma

### Soft Skills

- Time Management
- Communication
- Public speaking
- Leadership

# Hobby

# Bahasa

- Chess
- Drawing

- Indonesian Bahasa Ibu
- English Menengah

Powered by CakeResume